Hugo R. Greiner Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
Hugo R. Greiner Archives
1885-1941
IPAR.001105
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
10
The archives of Hugo R. Greiner composed of maps and stratigraphic sections.
Greiner, Hugo Robert
Biographical Sketch
Department of Geology, University of New Brunswick, Fredericton, NB, Canada. Yale PhD '54; Title: New York collector.
Description of the Material
Consists primarily of topographic maps from New York and Pennsylvania. Also includes some stratigraphic sections from New York, Ohio, and Pennsylvania
Connecticut; Pennsylvania; USA; Maps; Yale Peabody Museum; Yale University
- Maps, 1895-1941; Series I
  Scope and Contents
  Topographic maps from New York and Pennsylvania.
  - 1895-1910., 001108
    - Topographic map. Ithaca, NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1895; 002210
    - Topographic map. Elkland, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1900 (1926), 001957
    - Topographic map. Erie, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1900 (1943), 001958
    - Topographic map. Gaines, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1900 (1922), 001960
    - Topographic map. Girard, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1900 (1944), 001962
    - Topographic map. Dryden, NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1900 (1947), 001987
    - Topographic map. Salamanca, NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1900 (1942), 001996
    - Topographic map. Tioga, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1902 (1931), 001971
    - Topographic map. Cleveland, OH 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1903 (1950), 001949
    - Topographic map. Hammondsport, NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1903 (1951), 001991
    - Topographic map. Naples, NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1903 (1913), 001994
    - Topographic map. Naples, NY Quad. (1: 62500). U.S.Geological Survey: Topographic. 1903 (1908), 002030
    - Topographic map. Apalachin, NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1904 (1944), 001980
    - Topographic map. Chautauqua, NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1904 (1947), 001984
    - Topographic map. Clymer, NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1905 (1942), 001985
    - Topographic map. Jamestown, NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1905 (1944), 001993
    - Topographic map. Nineveh, NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1905; 002200
    - Topographic map. Warren, PA-NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1906; 001977
    - Topographic map. Angelica, NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1906 (1945), 001979
    - Topographic map. Linesville, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1908 (1917), 001964
    - Topographic map. Shenango, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1908 (1920), 001968
    - Topographic map. Warren, PA-NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1908 (1921), 001976
    - Topographic map. Bath, NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1910 (1944), 001981
    - Topographic map. Bath, NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1910; 002029
  - 1911-1920., 001109
    - Topographic map. Franklin, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1911 (1924), 001959
    - Topographic map. Stonesboro, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1913 (1926), 001970
    - Topographic map. Corning, NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1914 (1950), 001986
    - Topographic map. North East, PA-NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1915 (1945), 001966
    - Topographic map. Canaseraga, NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1916 (1939), 001983
    - Topographic map. Hornell, NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1918 (1950), 001992
    - Topographic map. Genesee, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic (Advance Sheet)., 1918; 002001
    - Topographic map. Hoytville, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic (Advance Sheet)., 1918; 002003
    - Topographic map. Montrose, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic (Advance Sheet)., 1918; 002006
    - Topographic map. Short Run, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500) U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic (Advance Sheet)., 1918; 002009
    - Topographic map. Smethport, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500) U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic (Advance Sheet)., 1918; 002010
    - Topographic map. Galeton, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic (Advance Sheet)., 1919; 002000
    - Topographic map. Ramseyville, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic (Advance Sheet)., 1919; 002007
    - Topographic map. Grover, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic (Advance Sheet)., 1920; 002002
  - 1921-1930., 001110
    - Topographic map. Trout Run, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1923; 001974
    - Topographic map. Randolph, NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1923 (1945), 001995
    - Topographic map. Cattaragus, NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1923; 002028
    - Topographic map. Bradford, PA-NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1924; 001952
    - Topographic map. Oil City, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1924; 001967
    - Topographic map. Tionesta, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1924; 001972
    - Topographic map. Ellicottville, NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1924 (1947), 001988
    - Topographic map. Franklinville, NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1924 (1932), 001989
    - Topographic map. Cambridge Springs, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1925 (1944), 001954
    - Topographic map. Meadville, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1925; 001965
    - Topographic map. Belmont, NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1925 (1943), 001982
    - Topographic map. Bradford, PA-NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1926; 001953
    - Topographic map. Towanda, PA-NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1926; 001973
    - Topographic map. Greenwood, NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1926 (1945), 001990
    - Topographic map. Wellsville, NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1926 (1948), 001997
    - Topographic map. Woodhull, NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1926 (1944), 001998
    - Topographic map. Monroeton, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic (Advance Sheet)., 1926; 002005
    - Topographic map. Troy, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500) U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic (Advance Sheet). [Volume=YPM.06342; IP.07413], 1926; 002011
    - Topographic map. Blossburg, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1927; 001950
    - Topographic map. Blossburg, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1927; 001951
    - Topographic map. Sayre, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic (Advance Sheet)., 1928; 002008
    - Topographic map. Youngsville, PA-NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1929 (1945), 001978
    - Topographic map. Leraysville, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic (Controlled Reconnaissance)., 1929; 002004
    - Topographic map. Tidioute, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1930; 002202
  - 1931-1940., 001111
    - Topographic map. Woodhull, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic (Advance Sheet)., 1931; 001999
    - Topographic map. Corry, PA-NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1932 (1944), 001955
    - Topographic map. Union City, PA-NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1932 (1944), 001975
    - Topographic map. Titusville, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1933; 002203
    - Topographic map. Genesee, PA-NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1937; 001961
    - Topographic map. Smethport, PA-NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1937 (1948), 001969
    - Topographic map. Coudersport, PA-NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1938 (1948), 001956
    - Topographic map. Cherry Creek, NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1938; 002204
    - Topographic map. Kane, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1939; 002201
  - 1941-1961., 001112
    - Topographic map. Kinzua, PA-NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1941 (1949), 001963
    - Topographic map. Sheffield, NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1941; 002211
    - Topographic map. Dunkirk, NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1943; 002205
    - Topographic map. Perrysburg, NY 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1954 (1979), 002209
    - Topographic map. Hinsdale, NY 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1961 (1979), 002206
    - Topographic map. Cuba, NY 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1961 (1979), 002207
    - Topographic map. Olean, NY 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1961 (1980), 002208
- Miscellaneous, Series II
  Miscellaneous archives including statigraphic sections.
  - Stratigraphic Sections., 001113
    - Stratigraphic section. stratigraphic sections, NY, PA, OH.: (in 3 sheets)., 1954; 002012
    - Stratigraphic section. stratigraphic sections, NY, PA, OH.: (in 3 sheets)., 1954; 002013